Stop right there. Before you can read, you have to find the right book.
And that's not always easy.
The people who bring the Scholastic Book Fair to your school are serious about helping you to find the right book.
Hey, Amanda, check this out. Scooby-Doo and the Mystery Mall, complete with 3D glasses.
You've got to see this.
Soon you're going to get a chance to visit the Scholastic Book Fair at your school.
You're going to find action, adventure, animals, aliens, awesome characters.
And some books that may just surprise you. Books that might help you see things in a whole different way.
And books that might encourage you to write your own story.
Plus, you'll meet people in these books who are really brave.
We're all out of time, but there are lots more books for you to check out at the Scholastic Book Fair.
Be creative. Use your imagination. Take your time. It's all about finding the right books for you.